Narrator: 9
Speaker: The match will be over at about 5.30.
Narrator: 11
Speaker: My alarm goes off at six o’clock every morning.
Narrator: 15
Speaker: We set off for the airport at 6.30.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: I want to give up chocolate.
Narrator: 1
Speaker: Don’t throw away that letter!
Narrator: 10
Speaker: Turn down the music! It’s very loud.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: Turn up the TV! I can’t hear.
Narrator: 7
Speaker: He looked up the words in a dictionary.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: Could you fill in this form?
Narrator: 13
Speaker: I want to find out about hotels in Madrid.
Narrator: 8
Speaker: It’s bedtime – go and put on your pyjamas.
Narrator: 12
Speaker: Could you take off your boots, please?
Narrator: 3
Speaker: My sister’s looking after Jimmy for me today.
Narrator: 6
Speaker: I’m really looking forward to the holidays.
Narrator: 14
Speaker: She works out every morning.